Hello friends, we will talk about women.
In this video, Justice has published a research report about Jeffries' favorite stocks. In
which he has
created an equity portfolio on some stocks. In it, he has
told in which
stocks he has
created an equity portfolio. Please like and comment. Friends,
you all know about Jaipur. It is
a global financial institution
and there is no need for any stock investor to introduce it.
I will update you. You can see Jaipur
is Chris Wood launches India equity
portfolio. Financiers, real estate and
stocks have the highest allocation. So, you can see
Christopher Wood, who is the head of equity,
that star forward global head
of equity shares, Jeffries has launched in
India long gown liquid form 16a
stocks similar to existing Japan and
China. Full course, so a portfolio has been prepared
for the long term where people are
thinking of investing or are going to invest.
16 portfolio stocks
are included in that portfolio. From finance to
oil and gas sector, energy sector and real
estate sector, he has mainly focused on it.
If this  The number is that Woodside itself remains
convinced that India is witnessing a strong new
housing cycle after seven years.
They say that this year's Josh Talks have
seen pressure, after which they are showing a halt in the
housing cycle's development.
All the investors said in the memorandum that this is not the right time to
invest in these stocks
because the Indian portfolio
Sensex is showing a halt in this time. But
despite this, they say that the stock market of
India, which is showing a possibility of a halt in the housing development cycle, is showing a
halt in this cycle.
Despite this,
they are
looking quite bullish on the Indian stock equity market.
You can see this in the portfolio.
Baby Toys stocks are 20% with
Reliance Industries, ONGC Oil, which has
set aside 70% for the real estate stocks
including Godrej Properties, Century
Textiles and DLF.
But along with this, the biggest investors have
given 40% financial investment, so if
you look at the heart today, this 40% has been
Given to financial with names like
ICICI Bank, SBI, HDFC, Bajaj
Finance, etc., approved and facial Ubud
tracking of these solar stars, a
portfolio has been prepared which
you are seeing on the screen in front of you. First of all, if we
talk about the financial sector, then
ICICI Bank, HDFC, SBI, Bajaj
Finance, ICICI Prudential, ICICI
Lombard, we used the internet and son,
you can see here, the highest weightage
report has been installed for free,
son, you are seeing this in percentage,
these people are also very special about the energy sector,
they have
kept G at the top position, in this,
government companies like Reliance and ONGC have been given 10
percent allocation to coal, in real estate,
they have given 85 percent and 4 percent weightage to Godrej Properties, Century Textiles, DLF Limited,
in auto,
Maruti Suzuki, Sarthak TV,
Motor Spinner, 55 percent weightage,
in consumer, they are very special about Jubilant Food,
in this single stock,
they have allocated 5 percent of the total capital
which is material.
In metals, they bought Tata Steel
with a position of 4% and
in logistics, against the government company
Shipping Container Corporation of India with 4
%, which is already a
strong disinvestment candidate of the government.
In the last month, we have seen a great rally here. The
stock has broken the level of 700 and is already
trending at a historical level. We have given
you an update about Jaipur's India
Equity Portfolio, which has been
chosen for the long term. You must be
understanding the meaning of long term. Extras like Jaipur,
these financial institutions,
when they invest
in any stock, they do not do it for 5 years, 10 years, 15 years,
which is why
they are expecting a lot of growth there.
If you have any stock and your
view is long term, then there are good news stories for you.
You are already thinking of
investing here, but the names of these stocks,
all the companies are big, you
too had made a plan to invest and are making a plan, so
in the long term, in this MP
in the long term, in this MPYou can buy here anytime, there are many great companies, so let's talk about this good news in this video, like the video and subscribe to the channel, thank you.